http://www.t1shopper.com/privacypolicy.shtml

T1 Shopper Privacy Policy
Your Privacy is Important to Us. At T1 Shopper, your privacy is one of our chief concerns. We understand that you entrust us with your private contact
information to help us match you with an Voice or Data Service Provider (we refer to all of these as "Carriers" or "ISP's"). In exchange for your trust, you expect and deserve our commitment to treat your information with respect. Rest assured that we protect your privacy. Under no circumstances will T1 Shopper sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except: as authorized by you, to participating Carriers, Systems Integrators
or other parties involved in your transaction, or as may be required by law or court request. The Privacy Policy below describes the standards we adhere to in handling information about you and your service request.
We want you to be aware of:
Who we are
Information we may collect on a T1 Shopper Web site
How your information is used
Altering the information you submit through a T1 Shopper Web site
1. Who We Are. T1 Shopper is the leading online voice and data
marketplace that connects consumers to Carriers that compete for their business across a variety of service types. There are more than ten participating ISP's
and Carriers on the T1 Shopper Exchange.
2. Information We Collect. There are several areas on a T1 Shopper site where you may be asked to enter both personal and non-personal information. We DO NOT sell or share any personal information about you to or with any person or organization except: as authorized by you,
to participating Carriers, Systems Integrators
or other parties involved in your transaction, or as may be required by law or court request.
Information we receive from you on service request forms. When you come to a T1 Shopper site to complete a qualification form you'll need to provide personal and some company
information such as your name, phone number,
e-mail address, location or other
information depending upon your expressed service requirements.
Technical information we collect. In request for us to ensure that we are providing the best possible consumer experience on a T1 Shopper Web site, we collect and track certain user information such as the time you placed your request, the type of computer and operating system you were using at the time your request was placed and for your security, the IP address you were using at the time of your request is recorded.
Information from surveys. You may complete a survey from T1 Shopper online. Participation in surveys is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us.
Information from the "Contact Us" section of a T1 Shopper Web site. You may contact T1 Shopper through the "Contact Us" feature. Participation in this area is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us.
Information we collect when if you
are a member of the T1 Shopper Privileges. T1 Shopper and our authorized
partners may collect information from you through our membership center. Participation in this area is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us.
Information gathered from Carriers. The "Carriers" section of our Web sites contain information for Carriers who wish to join The T1 Shopper Network.
Information gathered from the "Affiliates" section of a T1 Shopper Web site. The "Affiliates" section contains information for affiliates who wish to join the T1 Shopper Affiliate Program and advertise T1 Shopper's service on their site. If you would like to be an affiliate, you may submit an application containing personal information such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number and address.
Information collected from the "Calculators" section of our site. T1 Shopper makes several resources available to you to help you decide which service will best fit your needs. One of these resources is the "Bandwidth Calculators" section of our site. We do not collect any personal data you may input into to any calculators on our site.
Information we collect when you apply for a job at T1 Shopper. T1 Shopper may collect information from job applicants via the "Employment Opportunities at T1 Shopper" feature. Participation in this area is completely voluntary and it is your choice whether or not you wish to disclose your personal information to us.
3. How your information is used. We use the information you provide on your qualification form to match you with up to our participating Carriers, ISP's or authorized agents. We may also send your information to other third parties relevant to your transaction.  Carriers will also receive the technical information recorded at the time of your request. T1 Shopper may also share certain aggregated data with our Carriers and other third parties for general marketing and demographic purposes; however, this data DOES NOT include any of your personal identifying information.
Sharing information with our participating Carriers and ISP's. At your direction (when you click on the "Submit" button), the information that you provide to us on the qualification form will be sent through the T1 Shopper system and presented to our authorized participating Carriers who offer the types of service products you have identified, other parties relevant to your transaction and/or participating Systems Integrators.
As our Carriers and ISP's
may keep and use your information whether or not you choose to use their services, we recommend that you contact them directly for more information about their specific privacy policies.
Sharing information with third parties. We may also act as an agent for our participating Carriers and ISP's, sharing information on their behalf and pursuant to their instructions with providers of services related to your request. In addition, T1 Shopper may notify you about a special offer from one of our promotional partners.
Sharing information with authorized agents. At your direction (when you click on the "Submit" button), the information you provide to us on the qualification form will be sent through the T1 Shopper system and may be presented to our authorized agents. Our
agents are not in any way authorized to sell, share or give
your personal or company information with any other person or organization.
4. Altering Information You Submit Through a T1 Shopper Web Site. T1 Shopper puts you in control of your experience on our Web sites. You'll find our sites easy to navigate to find all the information you need to complete your transaction.
Changing your information. You may be able to review and change personal information in an active qualification form that you completed through T1 Shopper online.
Please e-mail us at "sales @ T1Shopper.com"
Deleting your information. We will delete all the information in our records at your request.
Please e-mail us at "sales @ T1Shopper.com"
Request to stop receiving e-mail's from us. Periodically, T1 Shopper may send you e-mails to alert you to money saving tips or special offers. If you do not wish to receive any of these offers, please e-mail us at "sales @ T1Shopper.com".
Security. T1 Shopper sites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
More Details
1.	Who We Are.
When you visit a T1 Shopper Web site to request a service, you will complete one simple service request
form. Based on the information you supply, T1 Shopper will transmit your data to participating Carriers who are best suited to meet your service needs. When you request the services of an ISP through a T1 Shopper Web site, we will transmit your data, including your IP address, time of service request and other technical details (see below "Technical Information We Collect" to
participating Carriers, ISP and/or Systems Integrators.
2.	Information We Collect.
Information we receive from you on qualification forms. Some of the information you supply to us on the qualification form may be optional. If you supply this information, it will not be sold or shared to or with any person or organization except: as authorized by you, to participating Carriers, ISP's or other parties involved in your transaction, or as may be required by law or court request.
Supplementary information for your qualification form.
In request for us to match you with participating Carriers and ISP's, we open a section up for you to place general notes to detail your exact needs.
This information is recorded.
Technical information we collect. When you visit a T1 Shopper Web site, our Web server sends a cookie to your computer. This cookie merely stores a limited amount of information about your site visit. The cookie merely tracks if you were referred to us though a affiliate site and who that affiliate is.  These cookies, however, DO NOT store any personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, etc. as you browse the site.
These cookies cannot be related to you as an individual unless you complete a service request
form.
When you complete a service request
form , we store your cookie identification in our system.
T1 Shopper also utilizes Web Logs to track aggregate information about how our site is being used. Web Logs track anonymous user information, including the number of visitors to our site, operating systems, Internet Provider addresses (if publicly available), and browser type. Unlike cookies, Web Logs are maintained only on T1 Shopper servers and do not store or place anything on the user's computer.
Information from surveys.
Every survey presented to you will include specific instructions regarding how your information may be shared. By clicking the "Submit" button at the end of the survey, you authorize T1 Shopper to share your data in the manner outlined on the survey.
Information from the "Contact Us" section of a T1 Shopper Web site.
In the "Contact Us" form, we may ask you for personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, etc. This information will not be sold to any person or organization. However, your information may be shared with other parties relevant to your transaction to help resolve any issues you report to us.
Information gathered from Carriers.
If you are a Carrier and you submit one or both of the forms requesting more information, your name and other identifying information will not be sold or shared with any person or organization. Your e-mail address or telephone number may be used by authorized T1 Shopper employees to contact you concerning your request.
Information gathered from the "Affiliates" section of a T1 Shopper Web site. Information submitted through the "Affiliate" section of our Web sites may be shared with certain marketing agencies for the purpose of helping us better serve the affiliates needs and provide additional
support for the affiliate sales channel. This would
enables T1 Shopper to develop and manage our T1 Shopper Affiliate Program more efficiently. T1 Shopper and our marketing agencies
do not sell or share your information with any other person or organization.
You will receive an e-mail from T1 Shopper indicating whether or not you have been approved to participate in the Affiliate Program. If approved, we will use your e-mail address to inform you of Affiliate Program news and updates. You may withdraw your membership from the Affiliate Program at any time by sending an e-mail to affiliates @ T1Shopper.com.  If you choose to withdraw, you will not receive any further e-mails regarding the Affiliate Program.   All request
placements take place on T1 Shopper's servers.
This allows us to have
complete control over the protection of
your data.
Information we collect when you apply for a job at T1 Shopper.
When you apply for a job through a T1 Shopper Web site, we may ask you for personally identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, etc. This information will not be sold or shared with any person or organization. All data collected will be used for the purposes of evaluating your application for employment. Your e-mail address or telephone number may be used by authorized T1 Shopper employees to contact you concerning your application.
3. How your information is used.
Sharing information with our participating Carriers and ISP's. After up to four participating Carriers and/or ISP's receive your information, they may contact you directly via phone, e-mail or other communications. All of our Carriers operate under federal and/or state laws and regulations and believe, as we do, that the Internet is an exciting and secure place to do business. If you are matched with any participating Carriers, the Carrier with which you choose to close your service may report certain information about your service
to T1 Shopper, and T1 Shopper will treat that information in the manner it treats the information you provided on your qualification form. As our Carriers and ISP's may keep and use your information whether or not you qualify for a transaction with them, we recommend that you contact them directly for more information about their specific privacy policies.
Sharing information with third parties. Following is an example of how T1 Shopper may act as an agent for our participating Carriers and ISP's. A Carrier may instruct us to share information with an Systems Integrator to prepare an proposal for the management of your corporate VPN. In such situations, we will be acting on behalf of the Client, under the authority of the Carrier's privacy policy, a copy of which you should receive from the Carrier. All of the information-sharing we do as agent for the Carrier would be permissible under applicable federal law for the Carrier to do directly.
From time to time, T1 Shopper may notify you about a special offer from one of our promotional partners. At your request, T1 Shopper will not send you any information or offers unrelated to your request for financing. If you do not wish to receive any of these offers, please e-mail us at "sales @ T1Shopper.com"
where you can easily remove yourself from our mailing list.
4. Altering Information You Submit Through a T1 Shopper Web Site.
Changing your information. If you want to change the type of service or make other significant changes to your request
form, you might need to make another request through our Web site.
Deleting your information.
At you request, we will remove your
request
form from our records.
If we make a change to our Privacy Policy in the future that will affect how we treat your information, we will notify you of the change unless you have requested to have your information deleted from our system.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on
April 19, 2003
Privacy Policy - T1 Forum - Customers - Terms Of Use - Network of Carriers - Traceroute - Byte Calculator - Download Calculator - About Us - Contact Us
Copyright © 1999-2014 T1 Shopper, Inc.™, All rights reserved.
This page is valid HTML 4.01 Transitional
